<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>STA 360/602L: SUMMER II 2020</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on STA 360/602L: SUMMER II 2020</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/syllabus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/syllabus/</guid>
      <description>Note: Please check this page frequently for updates and always remember to refresh the page.

 Date Lesson Slides (main) Slides (pdf versions) Reading Lab HW    PART I: INTRODUCTION TO BAYESIAN INFERENCE &amp;amp; ONE PARAMETER MODELS         WEEK 1        Mon, Jun 29 Course overview and introduction to Bayesian inference        Tue, Jun 30 Probability review and one parameter models        Wed, Jul 1 Drop/add ends         One parameter models cont&amp;#39;d        Thur, Jul 2 One parameter models cont&amp;#39;d; Loss functions and Bayes risk        Fri, Jul 3 Poisson model (wrap-up); Monte Carlo approximation and sampling        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Policies</title>
      <link>/policies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/policies/</guid>
      <description>When in doubt about anything at all, ask questions!!!
Prerequisites ALL students are expected to be familiar with all the topics covered within the required prerequisites to be in this course. That is, STA 611 or the following: STA 210 and (STA 230 or 240L) and (MATH 202, 202D, 212, or 222) and (MATH 216, 218, or 221, any of which may be taken concurrently). Students are also expected to be very familiar with R and are encouraged to have learned LaTeX or a Markdown language by the end of the course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resources/</guid>
      <description>Supplementary Textbooks These textbooks are great resources for some of the topics we will cover. You do not need to buy them, but you may be able to borrow them from Duke library should you need extra reading materials, besides the class slides and main textbooks.
 Albert, J. (2009), &amp;quot;Bayesian Computation with R (Second Edition).&amp;quot; Bolstad, W. M. and Curran, J. M. (2016), &amp;quot;Introduction to Bayesian Statistics (Third Edition).&amp;quot;  R and R Markdown Resources R Markdown can be used to create high quality reports and presentations with embedded chunks of R code.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>